// Question and answer data.
// local storage

const questions = [
    {
        question: "What famous magician died on Halloween?",
        options: ["David Copperfield", "Harry Houdini", "David Blaine", "Criss Angel"],
        answer: "Harry Houdini",
    },
    {
        question: "Where did the tradition of Halloween originate?",
        options: ["United States", "Ireland", "United Kingdom", "Mexico"],
        answer: "Ireland",
    },
    {
        question: "What does the word 'Halloween' mean?",
        options: ["Night of the Living Dead", "Ghost Gathering", "Witch's Night", "All Hallows' Eve"],
        answer: "All Hallows' Eve",
    },
    {
        question: "What were jack-o'-lanterns originally carved from?",
        options: ["Turnips", "Potatoes", "Pumpkins", "Squash"],
        answer: "Turnips",
    },
    {
        question: "What is now the most popular Halloween candy in the United States?",
        options: ["Snickers", "Candy Corn", "Reese's Peanut Butter Cups", "Skittles"],
        answer: "Reese's Peanut Butter Cups",
    },
    {
        question: "What does the word 'Samhain' mean?",
        options: ["Harvest Night", "End of Summer", "Moonlight Festival", "Day of the Dead"],
        answer: "End of Summer",
    },
    {
        question: "What is another name for a ghost?",
        options: ["Spectre", "Wraith", "Phantom", "Poltergeist"],
        answer: "Poltergeist",
    },
    {
        question: "In the movie 'Hocus Pocus' what are the first names of the Sanderson Sisters?",
        options: ["Mary, Sarah, Winifred", "Wendy, Mary, Sarah", "Sarah, Emily, Winifred", "Winifred, Sarah, Elizabeth"],
        answer: "Mary, Sarah, Winifred",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the officially named psychological fear of Halloween",
        options: ["Nyctophobia", "Samhainophobia", "Phasmophobia", "Hallophobia"],
        answer: "Samhainophobia",
    },
    {
        question: "How did early New Englanders protect their homes from evil spirits?",
        options: ["By hiding their shoes in the walls", "Lighting candles in their windows", "Setting out pumpkins", "Boarding up their doors and windows"],
        answer: "By hiding their shoes in the walls",
    },
    {
        question: "Which Halloween candy was originally referred to as chicken feed?",
        options: ["Candy Corn", "Chocolate Bars", "Wafers", "Mellowcreme Pumpkins"],
        answer: "Candy Corn",
    },
    {
        question: "These Halloween colors are representative of the harvest season and fire & warmth along with the end of summer, death, and darkness?",
        options: ["Orange & Black", "Yellow & Red", "Gold & Purple", "Orange & Blue"],
        answer: "Orange & Blacks",
    },
];

export default questions;
